[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is not  true about functions?", "correct_answer": "A function is always written as a polynomial.", "incorrect_answers": ["For some functions we can not find a maximal value.", "A function is a type of relationship between two sets.", "A one-to-one relationship is a type of function."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Adrian Viedts superhero identity in the movie Watchmen?", "correct_answer": "Ozymandias", "incorrect_answers": ["The Pharaoh", "The Egyptian", "King Tut"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first question that Bruce asked God at the beginning of the movie \u2018Bruce Almighty\u2019?", "correct_answer": "God, why do you hate me?", "incorrect_answers": ["Are you there at all, Lord?", "Are you kidding me?", "Hello, God, do you copy me?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nation won the fourth World Cup (of football/soccer) in 1950?", "correct_answer": "Uruguay", "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Brazil", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are male lions are generally stronger then female lions?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This black and white classic, starring Bela Lugosi is the first legitimate zombie film ever made.", "correct_answer": "White Zombie", "incorrect_answers": ["The Return of the Undead", "Zombie Killer", "Zombie Hunter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor was the first to portray secret agent James Bond in a movie?", "correct_answer": "Sean Connery", "incorrect_answers": ["Roger Moore", "George Lazenby", "Timothy Dalton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following cartoon dogs was a beagle?", "correct_answer": "Snoopy", "incorrect_answers": ["Courage", "Scooby Doo", "Clifford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Chunk gets locked in the freezer with the dead body in the film The Goonies, what else is in there with him?", "correct_answer": "Ice Cream", "incorrect_answers": ["Hanging meat", "Boxes", "Sloth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hilary Duffs character, Sam, is the Cinderella in the movie A Cinderella Story. What are the names of Sams twisted stepsisters?", "correct_answer": "Brianna and Gabriela", "incorrect_answers": ["Anastasia and Drizella", "Calliope and Minerva", "Marguerite and Jacqueline"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1974 film was the winner of the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 47th Academy Awards in 1975.", "correct_answer": "The Godfather Part II", "incorrect_answers": ["The Conversation", "Chinatown", "The Towering Inferno"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress was originally cast as Cady in Mean Girls, but the producers decided that she was a better fit for the character of queen bee Regina George.", "correct_answer": "Rachel McAdams", "incorrect_answers": ["Jessica Alba", "Jessica Biel", "Kiera Knightley"]}]